

Tran Van Kiet

- **d** Oct 10, 2001
- **6** 0585120478
- Binh Thuan
- Male
- kiet.tran101001@gmail.com
- Vinh Hao Commune, Tuy Phong District, i https://www.facebook.com/kiet.tranvan. 37604

OBJECTIVE

Shorterm(in the next year): Become a programmer for the company, never stop learning and improving programming knowledge to develop skills as well as complete assigned jobs.

Longterm(in the next 2-3 year): The practical work experience that I have accumulated will be the basis for me to achieve my goal of become a senior programmer in the future, bringing success to the company. If possible, I would like to apply for the position of Frontend developer in your company.

EDUCATION

MAJORS: INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Oct 2019 - May 2022

THU DUC COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

GPA: 6.5/10

WORK EXPERIENCE

VOLUNTEERS

2019 - 2020

SAIGON'S CHILDREN CHARITY

- -Give gifts to poor children
- -Donate to a children's welfare fund

SOME PROJECTS DONE DURING MY STUDIES:

2019 - 2021

THE PROJECTS

- -A website that sells phones
- -Application "Quan Ly Phong tro" on IOS
- -Application "Quan Ly Phong Gym" on C#

SKILLS

Teamwork

Basic English communication

Self learning

HONORS & AWARDS

Scholarships in the 1nd semester 2019-2020 2019-2020

INTERESTS

Explore new technology

Music

Read book

REFERENCES

Ngo Minh Anh Thu Lecturers of Thu Duc college of technology E-mail: thu.ngo@tdc.edu.vn

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

I'm able to work under high pressure Enthusiasm and passion are also my advantages